<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<tools>
    <tool>
        <name>lombok</name>
        <url>https://projectlombok.org/</url>
        <description>Project Lombok is a java library that automatically plugs into your editor and build tools, spicing
            up your java.
            Never write another getter or equals method again. Early access to future java features such as val, and
            much more.
        </description>
        <tags>
            <tag>util</tag>
        </tags>
    </tool>
    <tool>
        <name>JUnit</name>
        <url>https://junit.org</url>
        <description>
            JUnit 5 is the next generation of JUnit. The goal is to create an up-to-date foundation for developer-side
            testing on the JVM. This includes focusing on Java 8 and above, as well as enabling many different styles of
            testing.
        </description>
        <tags>
            <tag>unit testing</tag>
        </tags>
    </tool>
    <tool>
        <name>dom4j</name>
        <url>https://dom4j.github.io/</url>
        <description>
            Flexible XML framework for Java.
        </description>
        <tags>
            <tag>xml</tag>
            <tag>xpath</tag>
        </tags>
    </tool>
    <tool>
        <name>MyBatis</name>
        <url>http://blog.mybatis.org/</url>
        <description>
            MyBatis is a Java persistence framework that couples objects with stored procedures or SQL statements using
            an XML descriptor or annotations.
            MyBatis is free software that is distributed under the Apache License 2.0.
            MyBatis is a fork of iBATIS 3.0 and is maintained by a team that includes the original creators of iBATIS.
        </description>
        <tags>
            <tag>ORMapper</tag>
            <tag>sql</tag>
            <tag>database</tag>
        </tags>
    </tool>
    <tool>
        <name>Flyway</name>
        <url>https://flywaydb.org/</url>
        <description>
            Version control for your database.
            Robust schema evolution across all your environments.
            With ease, pleasure and plain SQL.
        </description>
        <tags>
            <tag>migration</tag>
            <tag>sql</tag>
            <tag>database</tag>
        </tags>
    </tool>
    <tool>
        <name>Jackson</name>
        <url>https://github.com/FasterXML/jackson</url>
        <description>
            Jackson Project is formerly known as the standard JSON library for Java (or JVM platform in general), or, as
            the "best JSON parser for Java." Or simply as "JSON for Java." More than that, Jackson is a suite of
            data-processing tools for Java (and the JVM platform), including the flagship streaming JSON parser /
            generator library, matching data-binding library (POJOs to and from JSON) and additional data format modules
            to process data encoded in Avro, BSON, CBOR, CSV, Smile, (Java) Properties, Protobuf, XML or YAML
        </description>
        <tags>
            <tag>json</tag>
            <tag>csv</tag>
            <tag>xml</tag>
            <tag>yaml</tag>
            <tag>encoder</tag>
        </tags>
    </tool>
    <tool>
        <name>Hibernate</name>
        <url>http://hibernate.org/</url>
        <description>MORE THAN AN ORM, DISCOVER THE HIBERNATE GALAXY</description>
        <tags>
            <tag>ORMapper</tag>
            <tag>sql</tag>
            <tag>database</tag>
            <tag>validator</tag>
            <tag>full-text search</tag>
            <tag>NoSQL</tag>
        </tags>
    </tool>
    <tool>
        <name>Swagger</name>
        <url>https://swagger.io/</url>
        <description>
            THE WORLD'S MOST POPULAR API TOOLING
            Swagger is the world’s largest framework of API developer tools for the OpenAPI Specification(OAS), enabling
            development across the entire API lifecycle, from design and documentation, to test and deployment.
        </description>
        <tags>
            <tag>API</tag>
            <tag>documentation</tag>
            <tag>OpenAPI</tag>
        </tags>
    </tool>
</tools>